

# David Obidu

# Software Engineer

I'm an energetic and passionate college student working towards a BS in Computer Science at Middlesex University and an ADSE at Aptech Computer Education. I aim to use my knowledge of web development, cross-platform mobile app development, software development & product development, combined with the experience gained from projects built, to satisfy the software engineer position.

🔀 daviderinayo@gmail.com

Lagos, Nigeria

in ng.linkedin.com/in/david-obidu

+234 8186511634

zeusmist.github.io

github.com/zeusmist

# **SKILLS (NOT LIMITED TO)**

нтмі

CSS

JavaScript

React JS

React native

Node JS

Firebase

Mongo DB

C#

Java

etc...

# **EDUCATION**

#### **B.Sc Computer Science**

Middlesex University, London

03/2019 - 03/2022 London

# (ADSE) Advanced Diploma in Software Engineering

**Aptech Computer Education** 

05/2019 - 05/2021 Lagos

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software engineer

## Self employed

01/2019 - 01/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed multiple personal projects.
- Developed and Updated multiple freelance projects.
- Improved programming skill considerably.

# Software engineer

#### Friyay

01/2020 - 12/2020

A web & mobile app dedicated to helping companies set goals, make plans, work together, and see progress. https://www.friyay.io/Achievements/Tasks

- Developed & Improved a lot of Tools used in the app. eg. (most of the GIDBF Tools).
- Implemented a lot of UI/UX updates.
- Wrote automated tests for the team to use.
- Fixed a lot of bugs.
- And lots more contribution to the team goals and motivation.

Contact: Joost Wentink - joost@friyay.io

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Chief Technology Officer Off My Chest (OMC)

05/2020 - 12/2020

A mobile app for users to anonymously express themselves to the world without fear of being judged. Available on all mobile app stores.

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Built entire project from scratch.
- Updated app to professional standard.
- Gained a deep knowledge of marketing and customer acquisition.

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### My Online Portfolio

zeusmist.github.io

#### Off My Chest

available on all mobile app stores

#### Nundio

nundio.herokuapp.com

#### My Company App

mycompanyapp.herokuapp.com

#### More on my Github

https://github.com/Zeusmist